<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hackerdemic</title>
    <link>http://hackerdemic.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on hackerdemic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 11:17:39 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://hackerdemic.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>20230530</title>
      <link>http://hackerdemic.com/posts/20230530/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 11:17:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hackerdemic.com/posts/20230530/</guid>
      <description>Hello, World! Hey there, Hackerdemic community!
Welcome to our brand new blog powered by Hugo, the open-source static site generator. We&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to launch this platform as a space to share knowledge, insights, and stories about the fascinating world of hacking, cybersecurity, and all things related.
In this blog, we aim to bring you valuable content that covers a wide range of topics, including penetration testing techniques, vulnerability analysis, ethical hacking methodologies, secure coding practices, CTF challenges, and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>whoami</title>
      <link>http://hackerdemic.com/whoami/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hackerdemic.com/whoami/</guid>
      <description>Basic Information Name: ATHL337 Professional Title: Cyber Warfare Operations Craftsman Summary: I am the National Director of Cyber Games for Raíces Cyber Org, dedicated to promoting cybersecurity education through engaging Capture The Flag (CTF) competitions. With a background in Cyber Warfare Operations and a focus on penetration testing and malware analysis, I bring expertise in offensive and defensive cyber operations.
Active Certifications: OSCP (Offensive Security Certified Professional) GREM (GIAC Reverse Engineering Malware) GXPN (GIAC Exploit Researcher and Advanced Penetration Tester) GPYC (GIAC Python Coder) GPEN (GIAC Penetration Tester) GWAPT (GIAC Web Application Penetration Tester) CompTIA Security+ CompTIA A+ C|EH (Certified Ethical Hacker) Expired/Retired Certifications: GCUX (GIAC Certified Unix Security Administrator) GCFA (GIAC Certified Forensic Analyst) Education: Associate of Applied Science, Munitions Systems Technology, Community College of the Air Force Associate of Applied Science, Cybersecurity, Community College of the Air Force Bachelor of Science, Security &amp;amp; Risk Analysis, Penn State Bachelor of Science, Information Sciences &amp;amp; Technology, Penn State Master of Science, Cybersecurity and Information Assurance, WGU Work Experience: Cyber Threat Emulation team member Cyber Planner for OCO and DCO aligned missions Section Chief of the Malware Exploitation Cell Key Technical Skills: Penetration Testing Malware Analysis Linux and Unix Architecture Risk Assessment Web Application Security Notable Projects: National Director of Cyber Games for Raíces Cyber Org Building the CTF for RaicesCON in October 2023 Achievements: Information Dominance NCO for the 67th Cyberspace Operations Group (2021) 1st Place CTF Team - &amp;ldquo;RAICES&amp;rdquo; 5th Place CTF Team - &amp;ldquo;Cyber Meme Force&amp;rdquo; - SANS NetWars DoD Services Cup Championship Language Skills: Spanish: DLPT Scores - 4 (Reading), 3 (Listening), 2 (Speaking) Personal Interests and Hobbies: Powerlifting Charity Work Contact Information: LinkedIn: LinkedIn Profile GitHub: GitHub Profile</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
